# JINGJING LIU

jingjingliu0121@gmail.com | 0482 714 186 | Permanent Resident | Working with Children Check Number: WWC2257832E

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jingjing-liu0121/

#### -Professional Statement-

Having 12 years of experience in the education field, I work as the first point of contact for students and parents. I specialize in communicating and building relationships both internally and externally. My high-quality service delivery gives me good feedback and makes the team run smoothly.

### ----- Key Skills -

Counselling; Interpersonal skills; Communication; Conflict resolution; Time management; Multitasking; Detail oriented; Bilingual (Mandarin and English); Administrative skills; Customer Service skills.

### Professional Experience

#### Crimson Education

**Senior Student Success Manager** 

Feb 2022-Present

**Student Success Manager (Client Coordinator)** 

May 2021-Jan 2022

- Serve as primary contact to the client post-sales, coordinate the relationship between students/guardians and the wider Crimson team.
- Have regular 1-1 online meetings with students to know their progress and difficulties.
- Respond daily to queries from students, parents and staff via phone, email, and web-based communication channels.
- •Keep parents (or guardians) updated on progress and ensure their satisfaction with the program.
- •Identify issues and take actions proactively to avoid problems escalation.
- •Coordinate service delivery processes, including onboarding students, tutors and mentors' allocation and reallocation, key dates reminder, internal essay review submission, etc.

#### **Achievements**

- •Received very good feedback from clients and team members.
- •Got honors in the performance review and was promoted to Senior SSM in 9 months.
- •Won around 2 per month upsells and referrals.

## Career Education Consultancy Australia Business Development Manager Feb.2021-Apr.2021

- •Started the Chinese student market, seeking new business relationships with agents and potential clients.
- •Held B2B presentations and business meetings with prospective clients as well as maintained close and mutually beneficial relationships with existing clients.
- •Researched market, established and updated marketing plan to ensure strategies are in place to enable growth.
- •Increased client database and stored all records accordingly.

## **Communication University of China' Nanjing (CUCN)**

Student Counsellor Oct.2011-May 2019

- •Assisted students in all matters: academic, mental, financial and proactively managed any risk factors for non-completion.
- •Conducted lectures, seminars and personal coaching on job-seeking skills for graduating students to increase their possibility of landing a decent job.
- •Established rapport with prospective employers to identify employment opportunities for graduating students and assisted employers to participate in the on-campus job fairs.
- •Kept track of students' employment status before and after their graduation.
- •Provided orientation programs to new students, assisting them to adapt to life and studies at CUCN.

#### **Achievements**

- •Collected and updated the student health cover information of 800 students each year without mistake.
- •Built students' confidence and improved their job-seeking skills through lectures and personalized coaching, I increased the employment rates of my school from 80% to over 90%.
- •Gave employment guidance to over 1600 students over the course of 7 years, which was outstanding in CUCN and required much anti-pressure ability.

Student Advisor May 2008-Sep.2011

- •Answered general inquiries about academic, social, and practical activities to be arranged by school.
- •Built and maintained relationships with companies and organizations to provide internship and fieldwork opportunities to students.
- •Communicated with foreign universities and coordinated with different departments to ensure the international exchange programs delivery.
- •Invited celebrities from various backgrounds to make speeches to CUCN students.

#### **Achievements**

- •Started the cooperative program with L'Ecole Multimédia, Limkokwing University of Creative Technology, Central Michigan University.
- •Solved the problem in course articulation in Disney College Program and ensured the program's sustainability. Over 100 students took part in this program in three years.
- •Developed many regulations and rules in relation to students' internship, thesis writing, cooperation with other institutions, some of which are still in use in CUCN.

Education		
Communication University of China		Beijing, China
Master of Arts: Media Education		2006-2008
University of Ji'nan		Shandong, China
Bachelor of Arts: English		2001-2005
——————————————————————————————————————		
Qualified Education Agent Counsellor	PIER, Australia	Nov. 2019